sky-tours.com 2018-10-12

# Privacy Policy | Sky-tours | Sky-tours.com United States

This privacy policy sets out how we use and protects any information that you give Big Sky Grup S.A.  d/b/a/  Sky-tours when you use this website.

Sky-tours is committed to ensuring that your privacy is well protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Sky-tours  may change this policy by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

This policy is effective from 25.May 2018.

What we collect?  

We may collect the following information:

We require only information to make your booking/reservation with the airlines and/or service providers and we may contact you by  phone or email.

Security  

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

How we use cookies?

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

For  any further information about Cookies please check our Cookies Policy.  

Links to other websites  

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.  

Controlling your personal information  

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:  

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, we show you what's mandatory and needed to proceed with your booking/reservation other information is voluntary and can be omitted.  

  * We keep your information in a safe and encrypted database and if no longer needed we will delete information unless you have agreed that we may use your personal information for marketing purposes to better serve you.  

  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at customersupport@sky-tours.com.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee  (EUR 15.00) will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to customersupport@sky-tours.com.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
